AXLE RODRIGUEZ

#31 Sned Compound, East Drive Marikina Height Marikina City

0906-2433-195

rodriguez.imaxle@gmail.com

° SKILLS °

Programming Languages

- HTML5
- CSS
- PHP
- JavaScript(ES6)
 Typescript
- C++
- ASP.NET

Content Management System

- WordPress
- Adobe Experience Manager
- Joomla

Database Management

- Maria DB
- SQL Server
- Oracle
- Postgre
- MySQL

Reporting Tool

- Crystal Report
- Eclipse Birt Report

Versioning Tool

 Git version- control system

Graphic Design Tools

- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- After Effect
- Power Director

PROFILE

Dedicated on Web Development with around 4 years' experience creating and maintaining functional, attractive, and responsive websites. Clear understanding of modern technologies and best design practices. Have a strong creative and analytical skills that can work as a team player, as well as independently with minimal supervision.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Tech Support / Programmer at 8Box Solutions Inc.

March – September 2015

- Developing CRM application using PHP that will fit to clients need.
- Creating Report for the CRM application.

Jr. Programmer at Accent Micro Technology Inc.

March 2016 - May 2017

- Focus on developing in house web application for the company's need using PHP (Codeigniter) as MVC framework and eclipse Birt report for reporting tool.
- Creating / querying data from Oracle database upon user request.

Web Developer at Concentrix

May 2017 - March 2019

- Develop EDM that follows the best practices for email.
- Work with ADOBE Experience Manager as needed for maintaining and developing client's sites.

PHP Developer at People Partners BPO Inc.

June 2019 - January 2020

- Web Development / Maintenance of client site using WordPress.
- Developing school base web application that will replace the current one that being used by the company, using React.js as frontend and PHP (Slim) as backend.
- Working with Rest API Web Services.

EDUCATION

B.S INFORMATION AND TECHNOLOGY

ABE International Business College

Aurora Blvd Cubao QC. / 2015